'assin Ben Alla

□ (+31) 616093622 | ■ yassinbenallal@hotmail.com | 回 YasBenAll | 面 yassinbenallal

Summary_

During my Bachelor's degree in Information Science at the University of Amsterdam, I gained extensive experience in the field of data science using the programming languages Python and SQL. Since then, I have applied my programming knowledge alongside my academic coursework by building web scrapers for e-commerce businesses and engaging in web development using React. I am currently pursuing my Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam and working as a Student Developer at the University of Amsterdam. I am experienced in using scientific software in Python, such as NumPy, Pandas, and PyTorch.

Skills

DevOps Linux, Git

Back-end Python, SQL, Flask, Firebase, GraphQL

Front-end React, Next.js

Programming Python, SQL, JavaScript, R Languages Dutch, English, German, French

Work Experience

Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

TEACHING ASSISTANT

November 2023 - present

- · Organizing working groups where I support students on assignment work about topics such as game theory, Markov decision processes, and reinforcement learning.
- · Grading coursework.

University of Amsterdam

Amsterdam. The Netherlands

June 2023 - present

• Working on progressing the development of a chatbot toolkit for experimental research.

University of Amsterdam

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

• Programming social robotics experiments at the Amsterdam School of Communication Research (ASCoR), primarily using Python.

Oxaigen Amsterdam, The Netherlands

DATA ENGINEER INTERN • Building data pipelines using dbt (SQL) for AI tools that will be used in the healthcare industry.

· Building APIs using GraphQL.

University of Amsterdam

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

TEACHING ASSISTANT

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

October 2019 - July 2021

July 2022 - September 2022

- Organizing working groups where I support students on assignment work about topics such as statistical analysis (SPSS) and programming (Python).
- · Grading homework.

Education

Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Aug. 2021 - present

- GPA: 7.8.
- · Following the Deepening AI track.

University of Amsterdam

MSc in Artificial Intelligence

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

BSc in Information Science

Aug. 2018 - Aug. 2021

- GPA: 7.7.
- During my minor Data Science at VU Amsterdam, I deepened my knowledge on various topics in the field of data science, such as Data Structures and Algorithms and Information Retrieval.

Committees

2022 Study Association STORM Amsterdam, The Netherlands

YASSIN BEN ALLAL · CV NOVEMBER 15, 2023

H	no	rc	Q,	Δ	M2	rd	C

July 2023 Kaggle Award for the Machine Learning Reproducibilty Challenge 2022

Extracurricular Activity _____

Web development The Netherlands FREELANCER Dec. 2020 - present

- Building web scrapers for e-commerce businesses.
- Developing websites using Next.js and Firebase.

Licenses Certifications

France Éducation international

DIPLÔME D'ÉTUDES EN LANGUE FRANÇAISE, B2

Issued Mar. 2016 · No Expiration Date

• Certification of French-language abilities on an intermediate level (B2) for non-native speakers of French administered by France Education International (France Éducation international or FEI) for France's Ministry of Education.

dbt labs

DBT FUNDAMENTALS

Issued jul. 2022 · Expires Jul. 2024

• Finished the the online dbt Fundamentals v2 course and passed the end of course quiz, which demonstrates fundamental understanding of models, sources, tests, docs and deployment in dbt.